Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar
and as
you must have seen in the title and thumbnail,
what topic is today's video going to be about here,
friends, if you have
clicked on this video after seeing the thumbnail, then brother,
I am going to tell you the truth, I am going to make you
face the truth that brother, the
scam that is going on here with regard to BFSI, the
scam
that is going on here with regard to BFSI,
brother, in today's video, I am going to
tell you here, brother,
what scam is being done with you, if
friends, you think that brother,
you have done a course in BFSI, which is BFSI, banking sector, insurance, here, many
companies, many
ATC companies are
conducting courses here, okay, you must have
seen in the title and thumbnail, brother, what
you have seen in the thumbnail, brother, there are
many good brands here which
currently
conduct BFSI courses here, the fees of which are here,
BFSI which  The course is of
three months, brother, it is said here and the
starting fee of it starts
from ₹000 and goes up to ₹1 lakh,
friends, its fee goes up here,
brother, if you do a course from any of these institutions which I have
mentioned to you in the title and thumbnail, then
you have to pay a fee from ₹000 to ₹1 lakh, in which they
claim that they will get
you a job in the banking sector,
brother, you will get training in it,
you will get a diploma in which there will be a
certificate, normally there is a certificate, it is
not a problem, it is not that heavy,
that is fine,
normally you will get a certificate in which you will be
given training, in which you will have classes, there will be
live classes, brother, I
want to tell you that brother, just like they
claim here that they will get you a job in the bank,
brother,
you can join it even without a course because
brother, the bank has a requirement of candidates, they have a requirement of candidates.  They are
not able to find
such a candidate who knows everything and they face
some problem in searching for the right candidate,
because of this what happens is that the
consultancy people provide it here
or they
tell the institute that provide us the candidate,
you can get them to do any course etc.,
we have no problem, but you can type with us, what will happen through this is that
you will teach the candidate here, that is, you will
teach him the entire skill, how to do sales, how
work is done in the banking sector,
what all is there in the banking sector, we will
provide complete information there, the
institute provides it to the candidate, then what happens is that
brother, they get typed here,
with Access, with ADAC or
with AU Small Finance Bank, there are many
private banks, you
can Kotak, you must have
seen many of my videos that HDFC
sales here  I can also get you the officer's job
here free of cost.
How can I get it,
I have already explained it in many videos
below. By
taking the WhatsApp2 course, they are selling courses worth up to one lakh and
selling them. They are selling the courses themselves
and are getting them jobs in the banking sector
and they also claim
that you will get the job in your home town.
Brother, do
not think at all that you will get a
job in your home town, especially for the people of
Bihar. There is
no job available in the banking sector in Bihar right now, there is
no hiring, so please do not get fooled by whoever
tells you that brother, give me money or
says anything else, brother, I have
vacancies available especially for Bihar and many other states. Friends,
you do not need it
myself. Friends, I had
taken the BFCI course here. I paid ₹1 in it, in
which I must have
seen five to six videos here.  I did
n't even look at that course here
because I didn't have any requirements,
I just took that course in a hurry,
after that I realized that there is nothing to be
found here, whatever
you want to study here, whatever you
want to go into the BFSI sector, whatever you
want to learn about it, its total
content is available to you, in the
ebook that I launched here, I have given you
complete information about the BFSI sector
step by step, in that
also I have told you in the interview
that how do you have to conduct the 10 interview
questions,
how do you have to answer them,
friends of BFSI, I have already provided complete information about it
in my ebook,
its
only price here is ₹ 669, here I have
kept its price only, if you are
interested in knowing about the BFSI sector
and
if you want to do a job as a sales officer in hdfcfund.com, the
link is given below  Or you will have
Google 2, you will have
good communication skills, you will be able to conduct the interview,
if you clear the interview, then brother, we will
get you a job free of cost, we do
not charge even a single rupee, only ₹, if you
want to purchase a book, you can do it,
otherwise there is no need for that also, if you know
everything then brother there is
no need for that, if you want to do the job of a sales officer, then
brother,
friends, let us talk about the
institute, brother,
what does the institute do for you, it provides you a course here,
brother, it teaches you, it does
not do this, no one will take 100% guarantee that they will get
you a job, okay,
everyone wants to sell their certificates, everyone wants to
sell their course, someone is selling it for ₹1 lakh,
friends, someone is selling it for ₹10000,
someone is selling it for 15000, they all have their
own placement here,
whatever happens here, brother, it is their wish,
they do it in any way  So what do you have to do here,
they have to make you sell the course
and brother, if they want to loot money from you, I will
not say that they loot money, by the way they teach the
courses etc., whatever they have launched,
they also teach, take live classes,
give notes etc., they
also give you certificates, but brother, if you
want, brother, you can do it on your own, there is
no such thing, I have also paid
₹1 to myself, brother, I am
telling myself that I have already been fooled by paying
₹1 to me, in which I did not get
anything, I did not need even one of them,
brother, because brother, I am already
providing it on youtube0,
you friends, please check out here once,
you will definitely find that 100% worth the course friends, the
₹ you have spent, you will find it worth it, the
BFSI course you have done
from these institutes, brother, I am not going to take names
because brother,
I also know that copyright can come, rest brother, you should see,
I have told you, if you want in future
If you also want to do BFSI
course then brother, don't do it at all,
just focus on learning here,
know a little about the banking sector,
what all happens in it, what
questions will be asked of you in the interview,
you just have to know about that, apart from this you are
not going to need any
certificate, anything, even if
you are a fresher, if you have experience, then
brother, both are eligible, you can try us,
you can connect with us, I ca
n't say 100% that you will get a job here, but
if you have sales skills,
friends, you
know how to speak well, friends, you
want a job, then brother, you
must connect with us once, you will 100% get a job,
and as far as brother friends are concerned about these courses,
brother, that is your choice,
brother, friends, I ca
n't call it a scam, though
friends, they teach you, they also teach you for learning here,
and brother, they
take your signature on the terms and conditions in advance, so that
next time whenever your course  If it gets
completed and you don't get the job, then brother,
you cannot file a case against them, etc., that's why they make
you sign the terms and conditions,
I have also signed it, that
brother, if there is no placement, then there will be
no guarantee from them, that's why
friends, I call it a scam,
rest brother, it is your opinion, whatever your opinion is,
you must write it here in the comment box, whatever your opinion is here,
you must tell it here once, rest you
can connect us, friends, whatever is my
experience, whatever I have experienced here myself,
I have shared it with you,
you don't need to spend so much money anywhere, you
can try it here once for free, rest friends, it is your wish,
what are your opinions, you must write it in the comment box, I
hope you liked this video
very much, if you liked the video then like it,
if brother, you have
not subscribed to this channel yet, then brother,
go quickly and subscribe to this channel, see you
next time, care